{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/3769","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"3769","name":"Motor City Casino - Assembly Line Buffet","address":"2901 Grand River Ave.","zipcode":"48201","owner":"Detroit Entertainment LLC","licenseNumber":"062159","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"150","coords":"-83.06762,42.33944","geojson":{"id":"3769","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.06762487,42.339437444]},"properties":{"name":"Motor City Casino - Assembly Line Buffet","owner":"Detroit Entertainment LLC","address":"2901 Grand River Ave.","zipcode":"48201","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"062159","establishmentid":"3769","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"150","most_recent_license_date":"2022-04-29"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"3721","name":"Motor City Casino - Radio","address":"2901 Grand River Ave.","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"3724","name":"Motor City Casino - Signature","address":"2901 Grand River Ave.","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"3720","name":"Motor City Casino - Second Service Bar","address":"2901 Grand River Ave.","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"3719","name":"Motor City Casino - Chromatic","address":"2901 Grand River Ave.","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"3723","name":"Motor City Casino - Infamous","address":"2901 Grand River Ave.","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"3722","name":"Motor City Casino - Spectators","address":"2901 Grand River Ave.","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"3718","name":"Motor City Casino - Head Lights","address":"2901 Grand River Ave.","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"3717","name":"Motor City Casino - Struts","address":"2901 Grand River Ave.","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"2314","name":"Motor City Casino","address":"2901 Grand River","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"3726","name":"Motor City Casino - Room Service","address":"2901 Grand River Ave.","zipcode":"48201"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"61239","inspectionDate":"2023-01-20T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-101.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be safe, unADULTERATED and honestly presented. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Dishonestly presented","subProblem":"","location":"AMERICAN STATION","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2023-01-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"violationCode":"5-202.13","violationDescription":"An air gap between the water supply inlet and the flood level rim of the PLUMBING FIXTURE, EQUIPMENT, or nonFOOD EQUIPMENT shall be at least twice the diameter of the water supply inlet and may not be less than 1 inch. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Air gap","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Less than twice the diameter of supply line","subProblem":"","location":"Wok Line Area","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2023-02-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide air gap that is twice the diameter of the drain line and no less than 1 inch."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"60833","inspectionDate":"2022-11-21T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"59815","inspectionDate":"2022-07-12T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-202.13","violationDescription":"An air gap between the water supply inlet and the flood level rim of the PLUMBING FIXTURE, EQUIPMENT, or nonFOOD EQUIPMENT shall be at least twice the diameter of the water supply inlet and may not be less than 1 inch. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Air gap","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Less than twice the diameter of supply line","subProblem":"","location":"Wok Line Area","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2022-08-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide air gap that is twice the diameter of the drain line and no less than 1 inch."},{"violationCode":"7-201.11","violationDescription":"POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL shall be stored so they can not contaminate FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES by:   \n(A) Separating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL by spacing or partitioning; (P) and   \n(B) Locating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL in an area that is not above FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.  This paragraph does not apply to EQUIPMENT and UTENSIL cleaners and sanitizers that are stored in WAREWASHING areas for availability and convenience if the materials are stored to prevent contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES. (P)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Poisonous/toxic material(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/with","subProblem":"Food","location":"SALAD STATION","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2022-07-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store toxics below and away from all other items."},{"violationCode":"3-603.11","violationDescription":"If an animal FOOD such as  beef, EGGS, FISH, lamb, milk, pork, POULTRY, or shellfish is served or sold raw, undercooked, or without otherwise being processed to eliminate pathogens, either in a READY-TO-EAT form or as an ingredient in another READY-TO-EAT FOOD, the PERMIT HOLDER shall inform CONSUMERS of the significantly increased RISK of consuming such FOODS, by using menu advisories, brochures, lable statements, table tents, placards, or other effective written means. (Pf)\nFOOD LAW SEC 6149\n...The food establishment may provide the following statement on selection information so that it is made pulblicly available: \"Ask your server about menu items that are cooked to order or served raw.  Consuming raw or undercooked, meats, poultry, shellfish, or eggs may increase your risk of foodborne illness.\"\nThe statements must be in a minimum of 11 point font and in a color that provides a clear contrast to background.\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Menu advisories","subItem":"for raw or undercooked food(s)/ingredient(s)","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"SUSHI BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2022-08-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"3-202.15","violationDescription":"FOOD packages shall be in good condition and protect the integrity of the contents so that the FOOD is not exposed to ADULTERATION or potential contaminants. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food package(s)","subItem":"Cans","problemDescription":"Dented, dented on seam or swollen","subProblem":"","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2022-07-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"ASIAN STATION","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"56856","inspectionDate":"2021-12-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.18","violationDescription":"A FOOD specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A) or (B) shall be discarded if it:  \n    (1) Exceeds the temperature and time combination specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A),              except time that the product is frozen; (P)\n    (2) Is in a container or PACKAGE that does not bear a date or day; (P) or\n    (3) Is appropriately marked with a date or day that exceeds a temperature and              time combination as specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A). (P)  \n\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Ready to eat, potentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Beyond consume by date","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2021-12-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"54281","inspectionDate":"2021-02-17T00:00:00","inspectionType":"COVID19-temp closed","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"53494","inspectionDate":"2020-11-16T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"52570","inspectionDate":"2020-08-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"51562","inspectionDate":"2020-04-21T00:00:00","inspectionType":"COVID19-temp closed","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"51299","inspectionDate":"2020-04-02T00:00:00","inspectionType":"COVID19-temp closed","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"49733","inspectionDate":"2019-11-04T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.14","violationDescription":"(A)  Cooked POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be cooled:\n         (1)  Within 2 hours, from 135ºF to 70ºF; and (P) \n         (2)  Within 4 hours, from 70ºF to 41ºF or less (P)\n(B)  POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared from ingredients at ambient temperature shall be cooled within 4 hours to 41F or less. (P)\n(C)  POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  received in compliance with LAWS   allowing a temperature above 41ºF during shipment from the supplier shall be cooled within 4 hours to 41ºF or less. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cooked food(s) cooled","subItem":"","problemDescription":"From 135 degrees f to 70 degrees F for more than 2 hours","subProblem":"","location":"BUFFET","subLocation":"Inside the WALK-IN COOLER","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-12-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-402.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a direct connection may not exist between the SEWAGE system and a drain originating from EQUIPMENT in which FOOD, portable EQUIPMENT, or UTENSILS are placed. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Backflow/backsiphonage prevention device(s)","subItem":"Air gap","problemDescription":"Not provided on","subProblem":"Sink","location":"BUFFET","subLocation":"Under the Prep sink","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-12-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"SUSHI BAR","subLocation":"Inside the Cabinet(s) (lower)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"seals","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"AMERICAN STATION","subLocation":"At the gasket/rubber lining","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-12-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"AMERICAN STATION","subLocation":"At the gasket/rubber lining","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"at work levels","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"BAKERY","subLocation":"At the Lights","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-12-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-305.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination by storing the FOOD:\n(1)     In a clean, dry location;\n(2)     Where it is not exposed to splash, dust, or other contamination; and\n(3)     At least 15 cm (6 inches) above the floor, unless otherwise approved.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s) in storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Exposed to dust, splash, or other contaminates","subProblem":"Not covered","location":"BAKERY","subLocation":"Inside the Walk-in freezer","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-11-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store in a protective manner."},{"violationCode":"6-201.16","violationDescription":"(A) Wall and ceiling covering materials shall be attached so that they are EASILY CLEANABLE.\n(B) Except in areas used only for dry storage, concrete, porous blocks, or bricks used for indoor wall construction shall be finished and SEALED to provide a SMOOTH, nonabsorbent, EASILY CLEANABLE surface.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily cleanable","subProblem":"","location":"BUFFET","subLocation":"On the floor Cardboard","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-12-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-204.11","violationDescription":"Exhaust ventilation hood systems in FOOD preparation and WAREWASHING areas including components such as hoods, fans, guards, and ducting shall be designed to prevent grease or condensation from draining or dripping onto FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Exhaust ventilation hood system(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Designed to allow grease or condensation from draining/dripping onto","subProblem":"Equipment","location":"ASIAN STATION","subLocation":"Missing Grease collection device","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-12-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"BAKERY","subLocation":"At the Equipment","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"walls","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"ASIAN STATION","subLocation":"At the Wall (back)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"DESSERT STATION","subLocation":"Inside the Ice cream freezer","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"47752","inspectionDate":"2019-05-06T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"44932","inspectionDate":"2019-01-09T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-402.12","violationDescription":"If raw, raw-marinated, partially cooked, or marinated-partially cooked FISH are served or sold in READY-TO-EAT form, the PERSON IN CHARGE shall record the freezing temperature and time to which the FISH are subjected and shall retain the records at the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT for 90 calendar days beyond the time of service or sale of the FISH. (Pf)\nIf the FISH are frozen by a supplier, a written agreement or statement from the supplier stipulating that the FISH supplied are frozen to a temperature and for a time specified by law. \n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Frozen fish record(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained for 90 days beyond time of sale","subProblem":"","location":"BUFFET","subLocation":"KITCHEN","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-06-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Maintain for 90 days."}]},{"inspectionid":"43939","inspectionDate":"2018-10-10T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-203.14","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be installed to preclude backflow of contaminants into the water supply system at each point of use at the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT by providing an air gap or installing an APPROVED backflow prevention device. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Backflow prevention","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Install to meet requirements"},{"violationCode":"3-402.12","violationDescription":"If raw, raw-marinated, partially cooked, or marinated-partially cooked FISH are served or sold in READY-TO-EAT form, the PERSON IN CHARGE shall record the freezing temperature and time to which the FISH are subjected and shall retain the records at the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT for 90 calendar days beyond the time of service or sale of the FISH. (Pf)\nIf the FISH are frozen by a supplier, a written agreement or statement from the supplier stipulating that the FISH supplied are frozen to a temperature and for a time specified by law. \n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Frozen fish record(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained for 90 days beyond time of sale","subProblem":"","location":"BUFFET","subLocation":"KITCHEN","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-06-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Maintain for 90 days."},{"violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135° F.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Dispensing utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"","location":"BUFFET","subLocation":"KITCHEN","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Relocate."}]},{"inspectionid":"41843","inspectionDate":"2018-04-01T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"BAKERY","subLocation":"Inside the WALK-IN COOLER","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"BAKERY","subLocation":"Inside the WALK-IN COOLER","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":""}]},{"inspectionid":"39938","inspectionDate":"2017-09-06T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Hot food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored below 135 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-09-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store above 135 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"6-404.11","violationDescription":"Products that are held by the PERMIT HOLDER for credit, redemption, or return to the distributor, such as damaged, spoiled, or recalled products, shall be segregated and held in designated areas that are separated from FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.(Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Distressed merchandise for return/credit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not separated from","subProblem":"Food","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-09-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate separation to prevent contamination."},{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"Items stored In front of","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-09-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove items from handsink.  Do not store items at handsink."}]},{"inspectionid":"38225","inspectionDate":"2017-03-07T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"Items stored In","location":"DESSERT STATION","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-03-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove items from handsink.  Do not store items at handsink."}]},{"inspectionid":"36401","inspectionDate":"2016-09-12T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Drainage system","subItem":"drain lines","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed according to law","subProblem":"","location":"CARVING STATION","subLocation":"Under the Handsink","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove and replace to be in compliance with law."},{"violationCode":"4-204.11","violationDescription":"Exhaust ventilation hood systems in FOOD preparation and WAREWASHING areas including components such as hoods, fans, guards, and ducting shall be designed to prevent grease or condensation from draining or dripping onto FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Exhaust ventilation hood system(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Designed to allow grease or condensation from draining/dripping onto","subProblem":"Equipment","location":"BAKERY","subLocation":"Missing Grease collection device","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to prevent grease accumulation/dripping/draining."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-25T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"3769"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}